<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Clinician Dashboard on</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/clinician-dashboard/</link><description>Recent content in Clinician Dashboard on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/clinician-dashboard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Understanding the Dashboard</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/clinician-dashboard/understanding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 11:44:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/clinician-dashboard/understanding/</guid><description>General Outline #
The SMART BEAR Dashboard is the graphical interface for clinicians to insert and visualize data collected from the daily activities of the patients participating to the project. The Dashboard data inserted come from different sources including: the Baseline Assessment, the physiological parameters and activity-related data transmitted from the devices, the responses to and scores of questionnaires.
An overview of the Dashboard pages is provided in Features An overview of the aggregated clinical data, including physiological parameters, responses to questionnaires, is shown in the Home page (see Features) A clinician can manage his/her patients during all the phases of the monitoring from the Baseline Assessment, through the data collection phase to the 6-months check-up visits (see Patient Registration, Exclusion Criteria, Baseline Assessment, Patient Management) Rule-based interventions for Cardiovascular diseases can be created (see Interventions) Analytics can be created and run (see Analytics) Clinicians can receive notifications about the managed patients patients (see Inbox) The users can create and manage GDPR-related requests, for their patients (see GDPR).</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/clinician-dashboard/features/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/clinician-dashboard/features/</guid><description>Home Page #
The Home page is shown in Figure 1 and is the first element showing up to the user. The Home page displays an overview of the statistics related to the managed patients see Figure 2.
Figure 1. Figure 2. A sidebar is visible on the left, It contains the following buttons:
Home. It redirects to the Home page. Patients. It redirects to the Patients page. Notebooks. It redirects to the Notebooks page.</description></item></channel></rss>