<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Help on</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/help/</link><description>Recent content in Help on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/help/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/help/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Troubleshooting #
1. Why can I not login? #
In case you cannot login, click on &amp;ldquo;Forgotten password&amp;rdquo; to set a new one. Also, verify you have completed the registration.
2. Why are the comorbidity tabs disabled? #
The comorbidity-specific tabs can be activated by ticking the comorbidities in Medical History.
Also a shortcut is featured to select the conditions:
Click on the orange button at the lower right corner of the tab A tab appears.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/help/faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/help/faq/</guid><description>Frequently Asked Questions #
Here are our answers to some of the most frequent problems and/or uncertainties users experience while navigating the dashboard.
If our answer is not helpful, or you experience any new issue, please remember this page is maintained up to date with your suggestions. Therefore, feel free to contact our technical team.
1. Why do I see the risk of exclusion alert? #
The risk of exclusion alert is shown when the profiling algorithm detects any element (e.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/help/glossary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 11:19:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/help/glossary/</guid><description> Attribute: a column of a tab CCM: Clinical Case Manager External CCM: a Clinical Case Manager that does not have access to the Dashboard and does receive the notifications concerning his/her patient Field: a label or a box to click on and fill in a page GDPR: General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 MoCA: Montreal Cognitive Assessment</description></item></channel></rss>