<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Operating the Dashboard on</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/</link><description>Recent content in Operating the Dashboard on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/registration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:28:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/registration/</guid><description>Utilization #
Click on the Create Account button in the Login form (see Figure 1 and Figure 2) and the form Start Signing up appears (see Figure 3 ).
Figure 1. The form for logging and registering
Figure 2. Click on Create Account
Figure 3. Start signing up here
Type a username for registration in the field under Enter your username, then click on Proceed to Self Register (see Figure 4 and Figure 5).</description></item><item><title>Login</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/login/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:28:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/login/</guid><description>After completing the registration successfully, log in to the Dashboard by inserting your username and password in the Login form (see Figure 1).
Figure 1. Insert username and password
After confirming you are not a robot by clicking on the reCaptha tab, click on Continue (see Figure 2) to open the Home page.
Figure 2. Click on Continue</description></item><item><title>Patient Registration</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/patient-registration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/patient-registration/</guid><description>Patient creation #
Click on the +PATIENT button in the Patients page at the upper right corner and the Create patient form appears (see Figure 1) and Figure 2.
Figure 1. Click here to create a patient record
Figure 2. The Create patient form
Follow these steps to create the record of a patient:
Click on the Pilot label. A dropdown menu appears from which the user must select a value (e.</description></item><item><title>Exclusion Criteria</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/exclusion-criteria/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/exclusion-criteria/</guid><description>General #
After a patient is accepted click on the +ASSESSMENT button (see Figure 80) and a new Assessment is generated. Click on the SHOW button and the Medical History tab appears, where data from the General Assessment can be inserted, saved and modified. This tab is divided into the following tabs:
General Info. It can be filled with data on comorbities Life Habits. It can be filled with data on Life Habits Physical Examinations.</description></item><item><title>Baseline Assessment</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/baseline-assessment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/baseline-assessment/</guid><description>Intro #
After completing the Dexterity and the MoCA, the following cases can happen:
The patient matches the exclusion criteria. No pop-up is visualized. The patient does NOT match the exclusion criteria. An orange popup appears, suggesting to NOT include the patient, click on the DON’T EXCLUDE to accept the patient anyway, otherwise click EXCLUDE button (see Figure 97). If the patient is NOT accepted, GDPR obliges to delete all the data, otherwise continue the Baseline Assessment.</description></item><item><title>Patient Management</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/patient-management/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/patient-management/</guid><description>Search #
The user can search a patient in the Patient page either by:
Clicking on the &amp;lt; (left) and &amp;gt; (right) buttons that are displayed on the lower right corner in the tab. (see Figure 209) Typing the patient id in the search bar on top of the tab. (see Figure 210). 👉 Typing the id in the search box is much faster ! In each row of the Patients tab the user can click on the following buttons that are shown in Figure 211, each redirecting to an element:</description></item><item><title>Interventions</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/interventions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:52 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/interventions/</guid><description>Management #
Rule-based interventions for Cardiovascular diseases can be created in the Interventions tab. Follow the steps below to create an Intervention:
Click on the +INTERVENTION button in the Interventions tab. The Create Intervention tab appears, where predefined values are set by default and can be modified if necessary (see Figure 247 and Figure 248) Click on Extreme Low Value and Extreme High Value under Systolic Blood Pressure and type the values (see Figure 249 and Figure 250) Click on Optimal Low Value and Optimal High Value under Systolic Blood Pressure and type the values (see Figure 251 and Figure 252) Click on Threshold value under Systolic Blood Pressure and type the value that triggers the Intervention (see Figure 253) Follow steps 2, 3, 4 again for Diastolic Blood Pressure values (see Figure 254) Page 130D14 - Report on SMART BEAR Cloud Enabling Components v1 Click on the SAVE button to save the data, otherwise click on the CANCEL button to discard them (see Figure 255) The new Intervention appears as a new record in the Interventions tab.</description></item><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/analytics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:30:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/analytics/</guid><description>Notebook creation #
The user can create and run analytics on the Notebooks page. Follow the steps below to create a Notebook:
Click on the +NOTEBOOK button in the Notebooks page. A form appears (see Figure 256 and Figure 257) Click on Name. Type a value (see Figure 258) Click on Description. Type a value (see Figure 259) Click on CREATE NOTEBOOK to save the data, otherwise click on CANCEL to discard them (see Figure 260).</description></item><item><title>Inbox</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/inbox/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:30:48 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/inbox/</guid><description>Management of notifications and subscriptions #
In order to manage the Notifications and Subscriptions, click on the INBOX button (see sec. 3.2.4). In the subscription tab, click on the button under SUBSCRIBED to activate or deactivate the messages from a patient (see Figure 267).</description></item><item><title>Gdpr</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/gdpr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:31:02 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/gdpr/</guid><description>Creation of GDPR Request #
In order to create a GDPR request, open the GDPR page (see sec, 3.2.5) and follow the steps below:
Click on the + GDPR REQUEST button as it is shown in Figure 268. The Create GDPR Request form appears that is shown in Figure 269 Click on the Patient ID label as it is shown in Figure 270. A dropdown menu appears, select a value Click on the Category label as it is shown in Figure 271.</description></item></channel></rss>