<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Operating the Dashboard on</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/</link><description>Recent content in Operating the Dashboard on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Login</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/login/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:28:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/login/</guid><description>After completing the registration successfully, insert your username and password in the Login form then click on Sign in.</description></item><item><title>Patient Registration</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/patient-registration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/patient-registration/</guid><description>Patient creation #
graph TD;
Start(PATIENT &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;CREATION)--&amp;gt;
ClickPlusMed(1. Click on **+PATIENT** in the Patients page &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; up to the corner to open the Create Patient form);
ClickPlusMed--See sec--&amp;gt;FillData(2. Fill the following data &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; to complete the form)
FillData--&amp;gt;Pilot(2.1 **Pilot:** Click on it and &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; select a value from the menu)
Pilot--&amp;gt;SbEmail(2.2 **SB Email:** Click on it and type the patient's &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; assigned email address to set up the devices kit)
SbEmail--&amp;gt;DateOf(2.</description></item><item><title>Exclusion Criteria</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/exclusion-criteria/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/exclusion-criteria/</guid><description>Intro #
In order to the include or exclude a patient from SMART BEAR, start the clinical assessment by administering the MoCA and the Dexterity (from the Health Utilities Index 3). The steps to begin the clinical assessment are the following:
Click on +ASSESSMENT and a new Assessment is generated. Click on SHOW and the Exclusion Criteria tab appears, otherwise click on DELETE to cancel the Assessment. Step 1
Step 2.</description></item><item><title>Baseline Assessment</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/baseline-assessment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/baseline-assessment/</guid><description>Intro #
After verifying the exclusion criteria are matched, two new buttons will appear in the patient’s record:
• DEVICES MANAGEMENT which opens the Devices tab. This tab allows the user to view, insert and modify the information about the devices associated to a patient.
• ID MANAGEMENT which opens the ID Management tab appears. This tab allows the user to view, insert and modify the IDs that are assigned to a patient in the context of the synergies with other projects, e.</description></item><item><title>Patient Management</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/patient-management/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/patient-management/</guid><description>Search #
To search a patient in the Patient page the user can:
Click on the &amp;lt; (left) and &amp;gt; (right) buttons in the lower right corner in the tab. Type the patient id in the search bar on top of the tab. In each row of the Patients tab the user can click on the following buttons:
• SHOW. It opens the Patient tab where the following buttons appear on the left • EDIT.</description></item><item><title>Interventions</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/interventions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:29:52 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/interventions/</guid><description>Interventions are functionalities that support the delivery of personalized alerts to a patient, based on the parameters thresholds to be set. Rule-based interventions are available, which means the user can set the thresholds manually.
Intervention creation #
Follow the steps below to create an Intervention:
In a patient&amp;rsquo;s record, click on INTERVENTIONS to open the interventions tab Click on +INTERVENTION, to open the Create Intervention tab Click on &amp;ldquo;Intervention type&amp;rdquo;, and select an option from the menu Set the required parameters, based on the parameter to be targeted.</description></item><item><title>Analytics</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/analytics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:30:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/analytics/</guid><description>Notebook creation #
Analytics are statistical tools that are the output of data analysis.
The user can create and run analytics in the Notebooks page. Follow the steps below to create a Notebook:
Click on +NOTEBOOK in the Notebooks page to open the Create a Notebook tab Click on Name and type a value Click on Description and type a value Click on CREATE NOTEBOOK to save the data, otherwise click on CANCEL to discard them.</description></item><item><title>Inbox</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/inbox/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:30:48 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/inbox/</guid><description>Management of notifications and subscriptions #
In order to manage the Notifications and Subscriptions, click on INBOX (see sec. ). In the subscription tab, click on the button under SUBSCRIBED to activate or deactivate the messages from a patient (see Figure ).</description></item><item><title>Gdpr</title><link>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/gdpr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:31:02 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://smartbear-unimi.github.io/sb-ui-doc/docs/operating/gdpr/</guid><description>Creation of GDPR Request #
In order to create a GDPR request, open the GDPR page (see sec. ) and follow the steps below:
Click on + GDPR REQUEST (see Figure ) to open the Create GDPR Request form (see Figure ) Click on Patient ID, select a value from the menu (see Figure ) Click on Category, select a value from the menu (Figure ) Click on About, select a value from the menu (see Figure ) Click on Inform, select a value from the menu (see Figure ) If necessary, type a description in the field Description Click on SAVE (see Figure ).</description></item></channel></rss>